clickinc.com 2009-04-19

# Affiliate Marketing Software – Privacy Policy

ClickInc.com has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This statement sets forth our information gathering and privacy practices for our site and the  ClickInc.com network.

### What Information we Gather and Where

Our site use several different forms that our Affiliates and Merchants can use to request information, products, and services. From these forms, we collect the following information:

  * Visitors' contact information
  * Financial information
  * IP addresses
  * Website urls

### How Secure is the Information We Collect?

ClickInc.com makes every effort to follow industry standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. It is in our best interest to make sure this information is not leaked or obtained by any other parties.

### What Do We Use This Information For?

### Contact Information

We use your contact information to send you information about our company and to get in touch with you when necessary. We also use the information we collect to improve the content of our Website and have a better communication with you.  Our site allows you to opt out of receiving communications from us and to choose what information related to sales or commissions you wish to receive. You will be given this choice at the points where we request your information. If you do not wish to receive future marketing mailings, please un-subscribe or let us know. 

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Websites. Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes. Our system doesn’t rely strictly on cookies but we do use them. The cookie can be removed by flushing your system and doesn’t harm in any way your HD.

If you are a Visitor or Member or a Customer we may use a cookie to save your settings and to provide customizable and personalized services. These cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information. Additionally, be aware that if you visit other Websites where you are prompted to log in or that are customizable, you may be required to accept cookies. 

We also use cookies to track sales and activity between Affiliates and Merchants. 

### Online Shopping

Customers can purchase products and services or register to receive materials, such as a newsletter, catalogue or new product and service updates. In many cases, you may be asked to provide contact information, such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and credit/debit card information. We will not sell or distribute this information to any third party individuals or companies. This information is securely stored and only used internally.

### Release of Personal Information in Extraordinary Circumstances

Except as provided for in this Privacy Policy, Service Provider will never share Customers' personal information with third parties without Customers' express permission unless extraordinary circumstances apply. With respect to the release of personal information, extraordinary circumstances may exist when the disclosure of such information is legally required or requested by a governmental entity, or when Service Provider, acting in good faith, believes that the disclosure of such information is necessary to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process, protect the rights of Service Provider, prevent a crime or protect national security, or protect the personal safety of its Customers or the public.

### Privacy Policy Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, our Website, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you via this page.

We value your opinions and feedback. If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, please email [support@clickinc.com](mailto:mailto@antispam.com).

#### Can I cancel, upgrade, or downgrade my plan later on?

Yes, there is no contract obligation so you can upgrade, downgrade, or cancel your service at any time with no penalty.

If you cancel any plan you will not be charged starting the next billing cycle.

Note: If you prepay for 1 year of any plan, there is no refund as the price is not pro-rated.

#### What forms of payment do you accept?

At this time we only accept VISA or MasterCard credit card payments.
